(Sheldon:)I'm not afraid to be alone.
(Sheldon:)On land.
(Sheldon:)On the sea, it would be terrifying.
(Sheldon:)Because of all the drowning.
(Sheldon:)- Sheldon.
- Fine, no more drowning talk.
(Sheldon:)I'll change the subject.
(Sheldon:)Who do you think would win in a fight...
(Sheldon:)...you or a shark?
(Leonard:)Look, I appreciate your signature blend of
concern for me and incredible selfishness...
...but if I get the chance to do this, there's
nothing you can say that's going to stop me.
(Sheldon:)Very well.
(Sheldon:)Things between you and Penny
have never been better.
(Sheldon:)I hope four months apart
doesn't change anything.
I should've opened with that, huh?